<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
  <name>Wait, That's a Moon!</name>
  <packageId>Nolabritt.ToDaMoon</packageId>
  <author>nolabritt</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
  </supportedVersions>
	<description> [revived for 1.1]
	
That's no space station, that's a moon!

So many eclipses, yet such clear skies.

Yeah, that makes NO sense.

So I've decided to fill in the space around our forcefully adopted homeworlds!

Introducing the ThatsAMoon Mod!

Features
- Adds (for now) three moons and an asteroid orbiting high over the planet, each with different characteristics and textures.
=> Gas Dwarf (Dunno if that's a real thing but it is in this game :P), a gasseous moon, devoid of a solid surface and home to an extremely dense atmosphere.

=> Destroyed Moon, a moon that was bombarded by asteroids early in the rimworld's development. Eventually, its orbit was altered so signifcantly that the moon was ripped apart by tidal forces.

=> Small Moon(first one added), a moon sharing a surprisingly large number of characteristics with our moon, just on a signifcantly smaller scale.

Future Features
- More interesting looking moons and asteroids. Our rocks will blot out the sun!
- Varied moon sizes and more detailed descriptions
- Moons more spread out around the planet (currently they tend to clump together if two moons spawn)

Known issues
- There's a bug that causes the moon to disappear when the camera moves far enough away from it (not zooming, I mean when you pan across the world). I'm currently workin on a solution for that :)

- THIS MOD REQUIRES A NEW SAVE TO SEE THE MOON

Credits/Terms and Conditions
A big thanks to dubwise56, the creator of the Marsx Mod[ludeon.com], for giving me the go ahead to use some of his code!

All of the terms and conditions stated in the above link apply to this mod as well!

If using this mod in a modpack/derivative work, please include my name and a link to this page. Thankya kindly :D [This is a continuation of AgentBlac's original mod to 1.1. forward all complaints to him...]</description>
</ModMetaData>